Good morning.
I was told that I can go to Tokiten's benefit today.
Um, tomorrow.
I've been thinking a lot about what I should say.
I've been thinking a lot about it.
But it's a little bit cold today.
But I'm so excited that I forgot all about it.
I'm so excited that I'm forgetting all that.
I'm really looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to it!
Yes, my name is Yuna Yoshijima from One Nav One Heart!
Well, today
I'm going to attend
I'm here for a benefit party
I've just arrived at the venue.
I've heard a lot of different things
I'm very nervous because of all the members of the advertising department.
Yuna is also nervous because I'm a member of the advertising department, but I'm also nervous because I'm a member of the advertising department.
I'm also a member of the advertising department.
I'm looking forward to talking with Ms. Tokise and the other members.
I'm really looking forward to talking with you.
I'd like to introduce today's personal attire.
Today is March 3rd.
It's the Doll's Festival.
I'm...
I was really looking forward to today.
I went to a clothing store yesterday
I went to a clothing store yesterday to buy some clothes.
It's so cute!
This is all white.
It's all white.
Well, it's a fashionable coordinate to match Ms. Tokise's.
It's a fashionable coordinate to match Ms. Tokise.
It's like a fashionable outfit to match Ms. Tokise's.
I've been looking forward to seeing you, so I'm very pleased with myself for wearing your cute outfit today.
I found the panel, so I'm going to go get it. It's cute.
I've found the panel and I'd like to go get it.
I'm going to actually go and get it!
I got in line for Kaname!
Kaname's face is so tiny, and her eyes are so big, and she's so cute.
So, you know, you're just so cute.
Are you there?
Come on in.
Here they come!
Hey, guys.
Thank you.
You've got something for everyone.
I love you guys.
Thank you.
It was fun.
You're so cute.
I'm so nervous.
I've been nervous all the time.
After we were done, we used cardboard to make a whiz.
I can't see my face.
But even after that...
He kept waving his hands at me for a long time.
He was so cute.
He was so cute! Okay, I'll go to Hitoka-chan now.
Hitoka-chan is really...
I love you so much.
Here you go.
Oh! Yuuka-chan! Hello!
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for coming again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming again. Cute! Cute! Cute! Cute!
Cute!
It was cute.
Next, next, next...
Oharu-chan is in line.
Oharu-chan
I really love her strong singing voice.
She's so cute!
I'm going to go in pink.
Thank you!
I'm getting more and more influenced by you and Oharu-chan.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
You were so cute.
We talked about Ichita.
So cute!
Me too.
What's next?
Hiyori's next.
I'm going to Hiyori.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hiyori is really, really great.
You're so nice.
Hiyori's here.
Hello.
Thank you very much
Thank you so much, it was so cute, so cute, so cute, I'm going to go to Jurya-chan. Hello! Thank you very much!
It was cute! It was cute! It was so cute!
Julia, I'm coming!
Oh, my God, you're so, so...
Julia, you are full of beauty!
Thank you!
It's time to go! Thank you very much!
Thank you! Thank you very much for your time.
So cute.
Oh, my God.
I'm off, Aki-chan.
I love you so much!
I love you so much.
So cute
I love "cute" I love "cute" I love "cute" I love "cute
Please take care of yourself.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm happy to tell you to take care of yourself.
I'm satisfied.
She was really cute.
She was smiling.
He was a little bit like, "Aww," and he was so cute. He was smiling. He was kind of, kind of, ahhh, it was cute.
I've just finished the second part of the benefit, and I'm going to the third part after this,
Bye bye.
I'm going to the third part after this, but I have time,
I'm going to have dinner with my favorite, favorite, cute manager.
Bon appétit.
Looks so delicious. I've never been in a salad pole restaurant before.
I'm back, back at the venue.
I've had a meal and my stomach is full.
I'd like to head to the samba!
I heard that you can take a one-minute video
I'm going to take a lot of video in one minute
I want to use the photo function
I'm going to use the photo function to take a lot of videos in a minute.
I'm off!
That's our customer.
Cute.
A customer, please.
Nice to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Cute.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Okay, the shooting is finished.
Please wait at the bottom.
I'm glad.
Watch out, watch out.
Cute. It was fun. Cute, dangerous, dangerous, cute.
It was fun.
Thank you.
Cute.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Cute.
Thank you very much.
You're so cute.
So, today, I had the pleasure of visiting the benefit party for Sakisen-san,
I was there as a fan,
It was a lot of fun, and I was allowed to go to the end of the event after the third part,
I was able to go to the last end of the show, but it was so much fun, and I was able to think about the feelings of the fans and everyone who always comes to the show,
I felt really happy.
It was really, really fun.
I definitely want to participate again.
Before I say thank you for watching until the end
I'm going to take a vlog at home, so please continue to watch after this.
I will continue to vlog at home, so please continue to watch after this.
I'm back home.
I came home.
I wore it at home.
Advertising department member T-shirt.
So, I was really fulfilled and in love today,
It was fun.
It was amazing. Publicity staff, you really are always this happy, aren't you?
Looking back on today...
The photo session.
They were really cute.
I was taking a video, I was...
And then the members came in front of me.
And they called me, "Oh, Yuna-chan! They called me, "Oh, Yuna-chan!
I thought, "Oh, they call me by name? I thought, "Oh, they call me by my name?
I was really happy.
I was so happy to see everyone participating in the photo session,
I was watching from the back with the manager and staff.
I was watching from the back with the manager and staff how everyone was taking pictures,
After that, I went out and got in the same line as everyone else,
I was really impressed and wondered what it was like,
It was a lot of fun, and I actually got to take pictures,
I actually took pictures and the members waved bye-bye to me at the end,
I felt so happy and it was so much fun.
I really can't talk enough about my happy day.
I really can't talk about it enough!
I can't talk about Tokisen-san enough.
So, for those of you who like Tokisen-san
And that scoring meeting...
I also have my own Yuna Yajima scoring session.
After the One Love One Heart concert.
There will be a scoring session,
If you have time,
If you have time, I'm looking for someone who can give a talk about Toki-Sen-san.
Love One is currently having a live performance of "Musha Shugyo" (warrior training),
We are currently doing a "warrior training" live concert, "Love One", "Hashtag Love One", and so on,
We have not yet decided on the specifics yet,
I haven't fully informed everyone about it yet,
I would like to go to various areas,
If you are in the area, please come and see LOVE ONE,
If you are in the area, please come and see LOVE ONE.
If you are in the area, please come and see LOVE ONE. Thank you for watching. See you next time at LOVE&'s live concert and at the benefit party at TOKISEN.
See you soon.